Cyril Johnson Woolen Company Photographs 6589 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Campaign to Promote American-Made Wool Products, 1958; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Between sessions of wool industry meeting, Boston, 1958, black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Between sessions of wool industry meeting, Boston, 1958. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts four men in discussions between sessions of a wool industry meeting in Boston, May 2-3, 1958. Industry leaders discuss campaign to promote American-made wool products with Robert S. Taplinger (third from left) of Robert S. Taplinger Associates. Left to right are: J.M. Jones, Denver, executive secretary, American Sheep Producers Council, Inc.; G.N. Winder, Denver, president of the Council (both Jones and Winder are wearing a tie that says "Eat Lamb Wear Wool"); Mr. Taplinger; and George Ott, Richard M. Ott & Sons, Boston, chairman of the Wool Promotion Fund of the Boston Wool Trade Association. 23 x 18.25 cm.
  - Item 3: American wool industry leaders set to launch extensive campaign to promote American-made wool products, Boston, 1958, black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 9)
    American wool industry leaders set to launch extensive campaign to promote American-made wool products, Boston, 1958. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts American wool industry leaders shown at Boston meeting to launch extensive campaign to promote American-made wool products. Left to right: S. Willard Bridges, The Top Co., Boston; W.L. Sorensen, Warren Woolen Co., Stafford Springs, Conn.; Edwin Wilkinson, New York, executive director, National Association of Wool Manufacturers; J.M. Jones, Denver, executive secretary, American Sheep Producers Council, Inc.; Leo J. Murray and Ed Mone, both of Douglas Mills, East Douglas, Mass. 23 x 18 cm.
- Exterior Views of the Mill, 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn., 1900-1910 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, 1900-10. Image depicts an exterior view of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company complex in Stafford Springs, Conn. Primary building is two-story brick, with a one-story attachment to the leftn and a three-story attachment on the far left. Horse-drawn wagon on the street on the right. 24 x 17 cm.
  - Item 2: Exterior view of Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn., 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Exterior view of Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, 1938-43?. Image depicts an exterior view of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company complex in Stafford Springs, Conn. Seen from this angle, in the foreground is a two-story brick building; behind it is a much larger three-story brick building that stretches down the street. Cars and truck parked on street; a few pedestrians on the sidewalk. 24.5 x 20 cm.
  - Item 3: Cyril Johnson Woolen Company with sign, Stafford Springs, Conn., 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Cyril Johnson Woolen Company with sign, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, 1938-43?. Image depicts an exterior view of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company complex in Stafford Springs, Conn. The sign in front of a four-story brick building reads: "Cyril Johnson Woolen Co. Fine Men's Wear "The Fabric's The Thing". To the right is the three-story brick building prominent in item 2 in this folder. Note the water tower also marking the company. 24.5 x 20 cm.
  - Item 4: Cyril Johnson Woolen Company from a distance, Stafford Springs, Conn., 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Cyril Johnson Woolen Company from a distance, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, 1938-43?. Image depicts an exterior view of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company complex in Stafford Springs, Conn. Complex is visible in the center background; residential houses in the foreground. The water tank reads "Cyril Johnson Woolen Co." although that is not visible here; see item 3 in this folder for a view of the tank from the other direction. 24.75 x 19.25 cm.
- Royal Tailors, 1962; black and white photograph (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, 1962; black and white photograph (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Printed advertisement, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, CT